Intrusive Thoughts is a thriller, horror film directed by Daniel Ruczko.
Intrusive Thoughts starring Kenneth Miller, Larry
Cedar, and Kristen DeVore Rakes.
A young woman tortured by jealousy is waiting for her husband to return
from work, while holding on to her last bit of sanity.
Stephanie, played by Kristen DeVore Rakes.
Alex, played by Whit Kunschik.
James, played by Antonio Leon.
Katie, played by Jayme Lynn Evans.
Voice #3, played by Larry Cedar.
Voice #1, played by Daniel Ruczko.
This is a list of American films that are scheduled for release in 2026.
Following the box office section, this list is organized chronologically, providing information
on release dates, production companies, directors, and principal cast members.
The film explores themes of suicide, mother, jealousy, schizophrenia, voices.
The tone is dark and intense.